spyhuman.com 2017-06-13

# Privacy Policy of SpyHuman | Disclaimer before using SpyHuman app

This **_privacy policy_** has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their **‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII)** is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy _law and information security_ , is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

#### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your **name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, social security number or other details** to help you with your experience.

#### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you _register on our site, place an order or enter information_ on our site.

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To **personalize user’s experience** and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your _customer service requests._
  * To quickly process your transactions.

#### How do we protect visitor information?

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers. Admin access

#### Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Google

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: https://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

#### According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site _anonymously_  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our **Privacy Policy** link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

  * Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
  * On our Privacy Policy Page
  * Users are able to change their personal information:
  * By logging in to their account

#### How does our site handle do not track signals?

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a **Do Not Track (DNT)** browser mechanism is in place.

#### Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?

It’s also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking

#### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the **COPPA Rule** , which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

#### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

#### In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify the users via email

  * Within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

#### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

#### We collect your email address in order to:

#### To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:

#### If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at :support@spyhuman.com

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

SpyHuman.COM

+91-9104979801  
support@spyhuman.com

Last Edited on 2017-01-04

#### You acknowledge having read these words in good conscience. If you have additional questions, contact us via our form contact.
